<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
     xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd"
     xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>n8n Automation Digest</title>
    <link>https://news2podcast.com</link>
    <description>
         Welcome to *n8n Automation Digest*, the podcast inspired by the official n8n blog — your go-to source for mastering workflow automation.

Each episode breaks down key ideas from the blog, covering practical use cases, platform tips, and emerging trends in low-code automation. Whether you're building your first automation or scaling complex processes, this show helps you stay sharp, save time, and do more with less.

Listen weekly, and if you haven’t yet, explore the full blog at n8n.io/blog.
    </description>
    <language>en</language>

    <!-- iTunes-specific metadata -->
    <itunes:author>n8n Automation Digest | Smart workflows for modern teams</itunes:author>
    <itunes:summary>
         Welcome to *n8n Automation Digest*, the podcast inspired by the official n8n blog — your go-to source for mastering workflow automation.

Each episode breaks down key ideas from the blog, covering practical use cases, platform tips, and emerging trends in low-code automation. Whether you're building your first automation or scaling complex processes, this show helps you stay sharp, save time, and do more with less.

Listen weekly, and if you haven’t yet, explore the full blog at n8n.io/blog.
    </itunes:summary>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:name>Acosta</itunes:name>
      <itunes:email>luis.acosta@news2podcast.com</itunes:email>
    </itunes:owner>

    <!-- Updated image -->
    <itunes:image href="https://acosta1991.github.io/newsletter2podcast/n8n/logo.png" />

    <!-- Atom self-reference -->
    <atom:link href="https://acosta1991.github.io/newsletter2podcast/n8n/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

    <!-- Example item (episode) -->
    <item>
      <title>Test Episode</title>
      <description>This is a test episode based on n8n's blog content.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 18:06:11 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1Nq6WqqDsc1i15S_kHpjqDtqbbaMPG3Q9" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1746468371727</guid>
    </item>

  
<item>
  <title>MCP will be the death of low-code automation, and other spooky stories</title>
  <description>If you have feedback or want to build something similar, contact Luis at Luis.acosta@news2podcast.com. 

In this episode of the n eight n Podcasts, hosts Alex and Chris delve into the promising yet complex world of Modern Control Protocol (MCP) and its role in the evolution of AI agents. They unpack the framework's potential to streamline user interactions with large language models (LLMs) while addressing critical challenges such as security vulnerabilities, high costs, and issues of backward compatibility. Drawing insights from Andrew Green's blog post, the discussion highlights the responsibilities vendors hold in securing their MCP servers and the implications of inadequate security measures. Moreover, the hosts explore cost management strategies when using AI APIs, emphasizing the need for technical optimization. As they navigate the intricacies of MCP, they also touch upon the difficulties of integrating multi-source queries and discuss potential pathways toward more effective multi-agent architectures. With an eye toward the future, they ponder how the rapid adoption of MCP may give rise to more secure, refined alternatives. Tune in for a thorough exploration of the hurdles and innovations that lie ahead in the realm of workflow automation and AI integration.</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 17:53:34 GMT</pubDate>
  <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=12YWwk0G_bxPuRxPdnFkdXqQ81vzql1dK" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg" />
  <guid isPermaLink="false">1753638814392</guid>
</item>


<item>
  <title>MCP will be the death of low-code automation, and other spooky stories</title>
  <description>If you have feedback or want to build something similar, contact Luis at Luis.acosta@news2podcast.com. 

In this episode of the n eight n Podcasts, we delve into a thought-provoking exploration of the Model Chain Protocol (MCP), inspired by Andrew Green's blog post, "MCP will be the death of low-code automation, and other spooky stories." Join us as we dissect the promising yet perilous landscape of MCP in AI agents, discussing critical challenges surrounding security vulnerabilities, cost management, and orchestration complexities. With alarming statistics on command injection flaws and unrestricted access vulnerabilities, we highlight the urgent need for fortified security measures and effective cost optimization strategies. The conversation also touches on the necessity of backwards compatibility and the implications of model supply chain security. As we peer into MCP’s future, we contemplate its role in production environments and the potential for established players like Google to reshape the protocol landscape. Tune in for a comprehensive analysis that emphasizes the evolving nature of this technology and the ongoing adaptation required to navigate its hurdles successfully. Don't miss out on vital insights that could inform your understanding of low-code automation’s future!</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 17:57:25 GMT</pubDate>
  <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1yoC7KAgAqTRjdocWBZL7ubHSB-K1C9Ss" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg" />
  <guid isPermaLink="false">1753639045716</guid>
</item>


<item>
  <title>MCP will be the death of low-code automation, and other spooky stories</title>
  <description>If you have feedback or want to build something similar, contact Luis at Luis.acosta@news2podcast.com. 

In today's episode of n eight n Podcasts, we navigate the complexities of workflow automation through the lens of Andrew Green's article on MCP—Multi-Channel Platforms. Join us as we unpack MCP's potential and the hurdles it faces, including security vulnerabilities, vendor accountability, and the challenges of cost management in a rapidly evolving landscape. Discover why the maturity of MCP is still in question, how it impacts users and vendors alike, and what the future may hold as the architecture adapts. From the need for robust security measures to the intricacies of backward compatibility, we delve into how teams can optimize their use of MCP while preparing for operational demands. Don't miss this insightful conversation that aims to guide both seasoned professionals and newcomers in leveraging no-code solutions for enhanced productivity. Tune in and learn how to navigate the journey of workflow automation with MCP!</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 20:28:09 GMT</pubDate>
  <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1bbxBALaJW92AT6x7PgitL8NwZvQjeFCX" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg" />
  <guid isPermaLink="false">1753648089953</guid>
</item>


<item>
  <title>MCP will be the death of low-code automation, and other spooky stories</title>
  <description>If you have feedback or want to build something similar, contact Luis at Luis.acosta@news2podcast.com. 

In this episode of "n eight n Podcasts," we delve into the complexities of Multi-Channel Platforms (MCP) and their role in the future of AI agents, inspired by an insightful article from Andrew Green. Co-hosts Alex and Chris dissect the promising yet challenging landscape of MCP technology, exploring its security vulnerabilities and the implications for vendors and users alike. We uncover crucial aspects such as the responsibility of vendors for secure practices, the pressing need for effective cost management in Generative AI, and the complications surrounding backward compatibility as standards evolve. You'll learn how optimizing API interactions can mitigate costs, as well as the limitations MCP faces with multi-source workflows. As MCP continues to mature, the outlook for widespread adoption remains cautiously optimistic, with the potential for more secure alternatives on the horizon. Join us for an engaging discussion that highlights both the potential and pitfalls of MCP in the rapidly changing world of workflow automation.</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 20:39:43 GMT</pubDate>
  <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1rQB3iAojzUR7G3yK4JQ9ePjA__-f2yVx" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg" />
  <guid isPermaLink="false">1753648783597</guid>
</item>


<item>
  <title>MCP will be the death of low-code automation, and other spooky stories</title>
  <description>If you have feedback or want to build something similar, contact Luis at Luis.acosta@news2podcast.com. 

In this episode of the n eight n Podcast, we take a deep dive into the intriguing blog post by Andrew Green titled "MCP will be the death of low-code automation, and other spooky stories." Join hosts Alex and Chris as they unravel the complexities surrounding Multi-Cloud Platforms (MCP) and their impact on low-code automation, especially in the rapidly evolving world of AI agents. 

From discussing the current challenges of MCP to exploring recent security vulnerabilities, the episode highlights the critical responsibility vendors face in ensuring secure access to their products. As Andrew sheds light on model supply chain security and cost management, the hosts emphasize the importance of optimizing API usage to avoid skyrocketing expenses. 

With an eye on the future, they examine the orchestration of MCP agents and the necessity for sophisticated tools like n eight n to navigate complex workflows effectively. As they wrap up, the conversation turns to Andrew's somewhat skeptical outlook on the future of MCP, emphasizing the road ahead is filled with both promise and challenges. Don’t miss this insightful discussion filled with actionable takeaways and industry insights!</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 20:55:10 GMT</pubDate>
  <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1ePDzNlnXZ3wYO3UtZQ1MX74htkUv9yF1" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg" />
  <guid isPermaLink="false">1753649710667</guid>
</item>


<item>
  <title>MCP will be the death of low-code automation, and other spooky stories</title>
  <description>If you have feedback or want to build something similar, contact Luis at Luis.acosta@news2podcast.com. 

In this episode of the n eight n Podcast, we dive deep into the complexities of Minimal Capability Protocol (MCP) and its impact on low-code automation. Inspired by Andrew Green's thought-provoking blog post, we explore the burgeoning world of AI agents and the challenges MCP faces, including significant security vulnerabilities and adoption hurdles. Our hosts engage in a lively discussion about what MCP entails, the implications of its immaturity for users, and the responsibilities that shift to vendors as they implement this evolving protocol. We also dissect the critical issues around cost management and the necessity for effective API interactions, as well as the limitations posed by a single-platform focus that could hinder multi-agent workflows. With a cautious outlook on MCP’s future adoption in production environments, this episode offers vital insights into the trends that will shape no-code automation and the crucial intersection between security, efficiency, and user experience. Join us as we navigate these pressing topics and equip you with knowledge to thrive in the ever-changing landscape of automation technology.</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 21:01:17 GMT</pubDate>
  <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=112HCTM-uHxZDyPieQyGbSih0w3bW2LJw" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg" />
  <guid isPermaLink="false">1753650077031</guid>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>
