<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
     xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd"
     xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>n8n Automation Digest</title>
    <link>https://news2podcast.com</link>
    <description>
         Welcome to *n8n Automation Digest*, the podcast inspired by the official n8n blog — your go-to source for mastering workflow automation.

Each episode breaks down key ideas from the blog, covering practical use cases, platform tips, and emerging trends in low-code automation. Whether you're building your first automation or scaling complex processes, this show helps you stay sharp, save time, and do more with less.

Listen weekly, and if you haven’t yet, explore the full blog at n8n.io/blog.
    </description>
    <language>en</language>

    <!-- iTunes-specific metadata -->
    <itunes:author>n8n Automation Digest | Smart workflows for modern teams</itunes:author>
    <itunes:summary>
         Welcome to *n8n Automation Digest*, the podcast inspired by the official n8n blog — your go-to source for mastering workflow automation.

Each episode breaks down key ideas from the blog, covering practical use cases, platform tips, and emerging trends in low-code automation. Whether you're building your first automation or scaling complex processes, this show helps you stay sharp, save time, and do more with less.

Listen weekly, and if you haven’t yet, explore the full blog at n8n.io/blog.
    </itunes:summary>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:name>Acosta</itunes:name>
      <itunes:email>luis.acosta@news2podcast.com</itunes:email>
    </itunes:owner>

    <!-- Updated image -->
    <itunes:image href="https://acosta1991.github.io/newsletter2podcast/n8n/logo.png" />

    <!-- Atom self-reference -->
    <atom:link href="https://acosta1991.github.io/newsletter2podcast/n8n/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

    <!-- Example item (episode) -->


<item>
  <title>MCP will be the death of low-code automation, and other spooky stories</title>
  <description>If you have feedback or want to build something similar, contact Luis at Luis.acosta@news2podcast.com. 

In this episode of the n eight n Podcast, we dive deep into the complexities of Minimal Capability Protocol (MCP) and its impact on low-code automation. Inspired by Andrew Green's thought-provoking blog post, we explore the burgeoning world of AI agents and the challenges MCP faces, including significant security vulnerabilities and adoption hurdles. Our hosts engage in a lively discussion about what MCP entails, the implications of its immaturity for users, and the responsibilities that shift to vendors as they implement this evolving protocol. We also dissect the critical issues around cost management and the necessity for effective API interactions, as well as the limitations posed by a single-platform focus that could hinder multi-agent workflows. With a cautious outlook on MCP’s future adoption in production environments, this episode offers vital insights into the trends that will shape no-code automation and the crucial intersection between security, efficiency, and user experience. Join us as we navigate these pressing topics and equip you with knowledge to thrive in the ever-changing landscape of automation technology.</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 21:01:17 GMT</pubDate>
  <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=112HCTM-uHxZDyPieQyGbSih0w3bW2LJw" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg" />
  <guid isPermaLink="false">1753650077031</guid>
</item>


<item>
  <title>7 Best AI Agent Builders: An Expert Market Breakdown</title>
  <description>If you have feedback or want to build something similar, contact Luis at Luis.acosta@news2podcast.com. 

In this episode of the n eight n Podcast, we dive deep into the evolving landscape of AI agent builders, inspired by an illuminating blog article from Yulia Dmitrievna, Eduard Parsadanyan, and Andrew Green. Join us as we unravel the complexities of these powerful tools that help organizations harness AI's full potential while overcoming integration challenges. We discuss the two main categories of AI agent builders—workflow-based and non-workflow-based—and detail how they effectively blend large language models with operational logic to deliver reliable, structured outputs.

We'll break down various platforms, from innovative startups like Dify and Vellum to established players like Camunda, illustrating how their unique functionalities can cater to differing organizational needs. You'll learn why utilizing an AI agent builder can save time and resources, helping teams transition swiftly from proof of concept to production-ready solutions. 

Additionally, we provide key insights on selecting the right AI agent builder for your specific requirements, considering factors like ease of use, integrations, and cost efficiency. Whether you’re a technical expert or a business leader looking to enhance workflow automation, this episode equips you with the knowledge to optimize your AI deployment strategy. Tune in for a rich discussion filled with practical takeaways and expert analysis!</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 21:08:55 GMT</pubDate>
  <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1246NcP7nrOuvCIfKl5jRwUIqyrjJoSPB" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg" />
  <guid isPermaLink="false">1753650535199</guid>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>
