<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
     xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd"
     xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News to Podcast</title>
    <link>https://news2podcast.com</link>
    <description>News2Podcast turns written content—news, newsletters, blog posts, and articles—into high-quality audio, allowing users to stay informed in a practical and accessible way. Using advanced artificial intelligence, we convert this content into podcasts with natural-sounding voices, making it easy to listen while you drive, work, or go about your daily activities. Our platform is designed both for listeners who want news and long-form content in audio format and for media outlets and content creators looking to expand their reach through automated podcasts. With News2Podcast, information reaches you in a comfortable and immersive way.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    
    <!-- iTunes-specific metadata -->
    <itunes:author>News2Podcast | Business</itunes:author>
    <itunes:summary>Newsletter Empresas is a daily podcast where two experts invite you to dive into the most relevant business news and long-form written content—newsletters, blog posts, and articles—drawing directly from sources such as the "Empresas" newsletter of the renowned newspaper El País. With an engaging, conversational style, the hosts offer reflections and spontaneous commentary on national and international events, providing fresh perspectives on the potential future impact of each story. Subscribe to stay up to date in the dynamic world of business information!</itunes:summary>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:name>Acosta</itunes:name>
      <itunes:email>luis.acosta@news2podcast.com</itunes:email>
    </itunes:owner>
    
    <!-- Fixed the image URL -->
    <itunes:image href="https://acosta1991.github.io/newsletter2podcast/01/news2podcast_logo_1400x1400.png" />

    <!-- Atom self-reference -->
    <atom:link href="https://acosta1991.github.io/newsletter2podcast/rss_01.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />


  
<item>
  <title>Write emails to humans, not inboxes</title>
  <description>In this episode of our podcast, we're exploring the art of humanizing marketing, specifically through the often-overlooked medium of email communication. Join us as we discuss how brands can transform their email marketing strategies by recognizing that each email address belongs to a genuine person with unique interests and demands. 

We kick things off by emphasizing the importance of obtaining explicit consent—showing respect for your audience and fostering trust from the outset. Dive into the concept of "email foreplay," where we highlight the significance of building anticipation and connection before sending out your messages. Learn how to offer exclusive content, tailor your emails to audience interests, and entice potential subscribers with value-driven freebies.

As we unpack the essentials, we stress the importance of clear communication, transparent intentions, and the goal of nurturing an engaged community rather than inflating numbers. Tune in for actionable tips that encourage personalization and relationship-building, ensuring your emails serve as valuable resources in your subscribers' lives. 

By the end of the episode, you'll walk away with key strategies to help humanize your marketing efforts and transform your email list into a thriving, engaged community. Don’t miss this insightful discussion aimed at reshaping the way brands connect with their audiences!</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 18:03:25 GMT</pubDate>
  <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1yhFVk13vylH8rSkmbj2mICS02jzhrYi7" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg" />
  <guid isPermaLink="false">1755281005171</guid>
</item>


<item>
  <title>"Unlocking Success: Customer Acquisition Strategies and the Power of Community Feedback"</title>
  <description>**Episode Description:**

In this enlightening episode of our Microsaas podcast, we dive deep into the world of customer acquisition strategies that can transform the way you launch and grow your product! Join us as we explore innovative approaches like soliciting feedback pre-launch to ensure product-market fit and delivering value to early customers who prioritize substance over style.

We discuss the vital role of community feedback in driving product development and how incentivizing beta testers can create a win-win scenario for all involved. The conversation shifts gears to backlink strategies, unpacking the risks associated with cheap sources and the essentiality of choosing quality backlinks to avoid penalties from search engines.

Discover the power of collaboration and the underrated impact of directory listings on lead generation. We also celebrate small wins, highlighting the motivation that comes from achieving initial milestones, and share inspiring user growth stories from personal finance apps. Listen in as we spill the beans on effective promotional strategies, including leveraging social media engagement and SEO tactics to boost visibility and conversion rates.

This episode is packed with actionable insights and practical advice for aspiring entrepreneurs looking to make their mark in the Microsaas landscape. Tune in for a mix of strategies, success stories, and the essence of community support in driving future endeavors. Don't forget to share your journey on Reddit and be a part of the conversation!</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 18:14:10 GMT</pubDate>
  <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1Yb4vDUSw5Tx-VcQImDW2DC84qR__HR8G" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg" />
  <guid isPermaLink="false">1755800050414</guid>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>
