<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
     xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd"
     xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Get Your First 10 Customers</title>
    <link>https://kurzify.com</link>
    <description>
         Getting your first customers is the hardest step for any MicroSaaS founder.

Get Your First 10 Customers is the podcast that helps you go from zero to traction by breaking down the top lessons shared every day in the subreddit micro-saas.

Each episode summarizes the most valuable posts and comments from real founders: how they found their first users, what channels actually worked, the mistakes they made, and the creative tactics they tried.

No theory. No fluff. Just raw insights you can apply right now to win your first customers and start building trust in your product.

🎯 New episodes every day.
    </description>
    <language>en</language>
    
    <!-- iTunes-specific metadata -->
    <itunes:author>Get Your First 10 Customers | MicroSaaS Lessons from Reddit</itunes:author>
    <itunes:summary>
         Getting your first customers is the hardest step for any MicroSaaS founder.

Get Your First 10 Customers is the podcast that helps you go from zero to traction by breaking down the top lessons shared every day in the subreddit micro-saas.

Each episode summarizes the most valuable posts and comments from real founders: how they found their first users, what channels actually worked, the mistakes they made, and the creative tactics they tried.

No theory. No fluff. Just raw insights you can apply right now to win your first customers and start building trust in your product.

🎯 New episodes every day.
    </itunes:summary>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:name>Acosta</itunes:name>
      <itunes:email>luis.acosta@news2podcast.com</itunes:email>
    </itunes:owner>
    
    <!-- Podcast logo -->
    <itunes:image href="https://acosta1991.github.io/newsletter2podcast/getyourfirst10customers
/logo.png" />

    <!-- Atom self-reference -->
    <atom:link href="https://acosta1991.github.io/newsletter2podcast/getyourfirst10customers
/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

    <!-- Example item (episode) -->
    <item>
      <title>Episode 1 - Just Hit $13 MRR 🎉</title>
      <description>
        In this first daily episode, we discuss a founder’s journey after one month: 73 users, 1 paying customer, and the SEO strategies that are starting to work.
      </description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=1Nq6WqqDsc1i15S_kHpjqDtqbbaMPG3Q9" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg" />
      <guid isPermaLink="false">1746468371727</guid>
    </item>

  
<item>
  <title>Micro-SaaS Reality Check: Early Wins, Real Pain Points, and Busting the Easy-Money Myth</title>
  <description>Sponsor: www.kuzify.com

In this episode of "Get Your First 10 Customers," we delve into the essential strategies MicroSaaS founders can employ to gain early traction and build a sustainable business. Join us as we break down insights from the subreddit dedicated to MicroSaaS, where we explore a founder's impressive leap to $13 MRR in just one month, harnessing powerful tools like listing sites, building in public, and SEO. We also analyze successful tactics from a sales data enrichment tool creator who achieved considerable customer feedback through trials and clear problem-solving.

As we navigate through various posts, we emphasize the importance of a realistic approach to MicroSaaS—a rejection of the “get rich quick” mentality for a focus on patient growth, customer satisfaction, and product reliability. We round off our discussion with actionable insights for founders, including early SEO implementations, customer-driven trials, and the significance of maintaining product integrity.

Tune in for a riveting episode that strengthens your MicroSaaS journey with community-driven advice and a grounded perspective on achieving those invaluable first 10 customers!</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 09:17:46 GMT</pubDate>
  <enclosure url="https://drive.google.com/uc?export=download&amp;id=15ZQVLc8pRAzY7_bcYl5FQpVV5CuPEf9B" length="1234567" type="audio/mpeg" />
  <guid isPermaLink="false">1755508666434</guid>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>

